<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MUJEaseUp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_outpass">Outpass</string>
    <string name="aboutText">Manipal University Jaipur provides a unique environment for students to grow under the guidance
        of experienced academicians and acquire creative, innovative and technological skills,
        which are required to make the students profession- and industry- ready.
        The curriculum is broad-based and students are allowed to register for many open electives from diverse streams.
        Education at MUJ is not just about books and classrooms,
        but also about overall personality development and honing special skills.
        A student can achieve and accomplish many goals because of the variety of facilities offered.
        Apart from gaining a degree that is recognized all over the world,
        a student actually graduates with an edge over the others, which is so necessary in today’s competitive world.

</string>

    <string name="aboutText2">MUJ students have their hands full, 24x7, with various curricular, co-curricular and extra-curricular activities happening all round the year. The campus is fully wi-fi enabled and boasts of a large, 120 PC Central Computing Facility. The academic process is completely automated, with an Academic Management System in place, which allows students and their parents to access their grades, attendance, etc., from the confines of their homes.  It also renders the evaluation and examination system highly open and transparent.

The faculty at MUJ is highly qualified and is assisted by an eminent and experienced Adjunct faculty. An Academic Advisory Board, consisting of highly placed academicians and industrialists from the state and centre, is in place, to provide the necessary expertise on all academic matters and for planning for future academic activities.

The spacious and state-of-the-art digital Library at MUJ is adequately stocked, with the requisite number of reference and text-books, a large number of national and international journals of repute, e-books and e-journals.  Students and faculty are given on-line access to many e-books/courses, from Pearson, NPTEL, Springer, etc.

Many indoor and outdoor facilities are available to students, for sports, cultural and technical activities outside the classroom, through various Student Clubs. The sports facilities include TT, carrom, football, tennis, badminton, squash, cricket, throwball, kabaddi, etc.  Intra- and inter-University matches take place regularly, throughout the year. The Music, Literature and Dramatics Clubs facilitate students to hone their creativity and show their prowess in the cultural arena, under the able guidance of expert faculty.  Technical Clubs like the Green Club, Robotics Club, IEEE Students’chapter, IE(I) and ICEIT chapters, etc., allow the students to learn and update themselves with the latest technologies and showcase their abilities in various fields, outside their scope of study.

MUJ boasts of world-class infrastructure, with Hostels designed by world renowned architect, Ar. Hafeez Contractor and offering the very best facilities to students, including wi-fi, laundrette, tuckshop and multi-cuisine outlets. The Food Court is a unique concept at MUJ, where students can have their meals and other eatables of their choice. The Menu is finalised by the students through representation in the Mess committee.  The Student Activity Area (SAC), the Central Vista and the Amphitheatre are places where students collect during their off-class hours and think, imagine, connect, reflect, network and innovate.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_query">Query</string>
</resources>
